bidplacesb.com 2009-04-08

# BidPlace SB

BidPlace SB is owned by Advertising.com, a wholly owned subsidiary of AOL. The following statement describes the overall company practices of Advertising.com, including advertising on our network of websites, as well as across other internal sites, and products and services that are offered by Advertising.com. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Advertising.com does not own or control, or to people that Advertising.com does not employ.

#### Information Collected By Advertising.com

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data

Advertising.com delivers advertisements across multiple channels and media, including to web surfers who visit the largest third-party network in the industry - AOL's Advertising.com. With respect to individuals who visit those sites, we, and/or one or more of our third party vendors, may collect what is known as "Click Stream Data." Click Stream Data is anonymous, and includes information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us or our third party advertising technology vendor. We, and/or a third party advertising technology vendor, may use different types of technologies to collect this type of information, including cookies and web beacons (1x1 pixels).

In addition to the Click Stream Data collected across our web network, Advertising.com owns numerous websites and services, and often runs promotions and sweepstakes offers through various Internet channels (collectively referred to as "Advertising.com Properties"), and collects information at those sites. As a part of the registration process at the Advertising.com Properties, we may request and collect additional non-personally identifiable information about the visitor. Examples of the non-personally identifiable data that may be requested include age, gender, and interests. None of the foregoing information (collectively referred to as "non-personally identifiable data"), by itself, or together, can by its nature be tracked to a specific individual. Web surfers may elect not to provide Click Stream Data by following the Cookie Opt-Out procedures set forth below. In addition, web surfers who have provided registration data to Advertising.com may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the Data Opt-Out procedures set forth below. Personally identifiable information that is collected at the Advertising.com Properties is discussed immediately below.

#### Personally Identifiable Consumer Data

At some of the Advertising.com Properties, we ask people to register and provide personally identifiable data. Advertising.com is committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all consumers before the personally identifiable data is collected, and that they have opted-in to our use of their data. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, and email address. Web surfers who have provided personally identifiable data may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the Data Opt-Out procedures set forth below.

#### Other Information that is Collected

At some Advertising.com Properties, including this one, Advertising.com collects personal information on individuals and companies who want to enter into business relationships with Advertising.com ("business information"). An example of this would include web publishers who want to become a part of Advertising.com's web network. We maintain business information for purposes of administering the program, such as maintaining account information, sending payments, etc. We may share business information with third parties who provide administrative services (and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information), as well as pursuant to a court order or to law enforcement or government officials as we deem necessary or appropriate.

#### How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable data that Advertising.com and/or its third party advertising vendor collect are used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements to people accross the different websites they visit. Advertising.com may also use the non-personally identifiable data to better target content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If a consumer elects to provide Advertising.com with personally identifiable data, we may utilize such data for marketing purposes. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to that consumer's preferences and behaviors, and for other Advertising.com sales and marketing efforts.

#### Sharing With Third Parties

All personally identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in confidence by Advertising.com. There are instances, however, in which personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. The non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of Advertising.com on an anonymous basis.

With respect to personally identifiable information, Advertising.com may, from time to time, provide information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and pay-outs, or for other services related to providing an Advertising.com product or service. Any third-party vendor so used will be required to enter into a confidentiality agreement with Advertising.com.

Advertising.com may also share personally identifiable information with third parties who enter into business relationships with us. These business partners may include financial service providers (including credit bureaus and insurance agents); non-financial companies (including retailers, online and offline advertisers, membership list vendors, direct marketers and publishers); companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, and others such as non-profit organizations. We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service signed up for, if we decide to stop providing such services ourselves. In such situations, we will provide our subscribers with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that Advertising.com is very careful about which companies it does business with.

In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that Advertising.com, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that's the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information. Finally, Advertising.com may share information on individuals as it deems necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

#### Third-Party Advertising Technology Vendors

Advertising.com also works with various third party advertising technology vendors. These vendors may also use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect Click Stream Data. Please click on the links below to learn more about these vendors:

  * Doubleclick
  * Neilson/Netratings
  * Omniture

#### Security Precautions

Advertising.com makes significant efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure the high security standards. Any data that is stored on Advertising.com's servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. Advertising.com has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

#### Consumer Choice

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out

Advertising.com uses technology, including technology from its third party advertising vendor, which includes cookies and web beacons (1x1 pixels), to deliver better, targeted marketing messages to the web surfer. These tools are used to collect non-personally identifiable data to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. We believe that the use of such tools assists in providing a more meaningful web-surfing experience, but you may opt-out of the use of Advertising.com cookies and those of our third party advertising technology vendor if you would like. To do so, you can disable cookies on your browser. Alternatively, you can opt-out of Advertising.com's cookies by going to the opt-out section at this site, and you may [opt-out](http://www.advertising.com/abt_privacy_opt.php) of our third party advertising technology vendors' cookies by going to the "Third Party Advertising Technology Vendors" Section, above, and linking on a specific vendor's name. (For more information on cookies and web beacons, please refer to the [FAQ section](http://www.advertising.com/abt_privacy_faq.php)).

#### Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Opt-Out

If a consumer elects to provide Advertising.com with personally identifiable data, he or she has the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such data described herein or may have such data deleted in its entirety at any time. Simply contact us and provide the name of the service for which you provided information and let us know what level of opt-out you would like to exercise. These include: (1) Do not share information about me with business partners, (2) Do not solicit me with special offers other than those related to the service I signed up for, or (3) Remove my data from your database for such service completely. Once we receive this instruction, we will promptly take corrective action. Please note that we will need you to provide your email address or other previously provided personal identifier in order to identify you in the [Data Opt-Out](http://www.advertising.com/abt_privacy_opt.php) process. Also, please remember that if you choose to delete your information completely you will no longer receive the Advertising.com service in question.

#### Access to Data

Advertising.com allows consumers who have voluntarily provided personally identifiable data access to their data to ensure that it is correct and to make any changes. Please contact us.

#### Miscellaneous

#### Children's Privacy

Advertising.com is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Advertising.com's websites, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided Advertising.com with personally identifiable data, or registered at one of Advertising.com's websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us.

#### A Special Note About the European Union

European Union web surfers understand and consent to the processing of personal information in the United States.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

The issue of privacy is an evolving one. Advertising.com is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company's privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy that discloses the changes.

#### Effective Date: 

This Privacy Policy has been in effect since May 26, 2006.
